Michaela Vojtová

JUNIOR WEB DEVELOPER

Professional Summary

I'm a self-taught Web Developer constantly improving my technical skills and logical thinking. Currently I'm enrolled in Web Development course at Wild Code School in Lisbon, with a main focus of building projects in teams using latest technologies: HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, React.js, Express.js, Node.js and MySQL Database. I worked in diverse environments in different countries improving my skills on high level communication, customer satisfaction, problem solving and team work. In my spare time I practice singing; I'm passionate about music and that drove me to get an associate degree at Prague Conservatory.

Employment History

Remote Technical Support Advisor, Teleperformance, Greece

AUGUST 2020 — DECEMBER 2020

• Trained in MacOS operating system and related products. • Troubleshooting system and network problems. • Diagnosing hardware or software faults. • Set up new user's accounts and deal with password issues. • Rapidly establish a good working relationship with customers. • Get quickly to the root of their problem.

Cocktail Server, Mar Calma, Port de Pollenca, Mallorca

JUNE 2019 - SEPTEMBER 2020

Responsible for providing beverage service to all customers.
 Displaying a high standard
of customer service.
 Preparation of drink orders.
 Presented check for payment and
provided change.

Bakery Clerk, Pekárna Nostress Bakery, Prague

SEPTEMBER 2018 — FEBRUARY 2019

• Assist customers with product selection. • Share product knowledge with customers. • Make recommendations and suggestions based on customer needs. • Prepare coffee and other beverages. • Answering phones. • Taking orders and processing cash transactions. • Tracking expiration dates. • Maintain cleanliness.

Hotel Entertainer, Acttiv, Alcúdia, Mallorca

JULY 2018 — SEPTEMBER 2018

• Responsible for meeting and greeting guests. • Taking part in fitness activities such as zumba, acquagym and watersports. • Leading stretching exercise lessons. • Partly responsible for organising sport activities, tournaments of darts, football. • Performing regularly - singing, dancing.

Education

Web and mobile development training, Wild Code School, Lisbon

SEPTEMBER 2021 — FEBRUARY 2022

Web Development at Wild Code School is an intensive five months course that focus on learning HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React.js, Node.js, Express.js, MySQL, Git Bash and GitHub. The purpose of this course is to practice those skills on group projects. As a final task we build a project for a company.

Associate's degree, pop-music, Prague Conservatory, Prague

SEPTEMBER 2013 — JUNE 2019

I dedicated six years of studying popular music and singing at Prague Conservatory. I learned modern vocal techniques, acting, dancing, methodology of teaching, history of music and music theory.

Courses

HTML/CSS Bootcamp - Udemy

Tourism Entertainment Online Course, 80 hours - Acttiv



Details

+420 739 800 157 misacastella@gmail.com

Links

<u>Linkedin</u>

<u>GitHub</u>

<u>Projects</u>

Hard Skills

HTML & CSS

JavaScript

React

Git

GitHub

Node.js

Express.js

MySQL

Languages

Czech

English

Spanish